20世紀的巴克.羅傑斯
Buck Rogers in the 20th century!
巴克.羅傑斯，這是二十世紀裡的 一次奇遇
Buck Rogers, now adventuring in the amazing world of the 20th century.
通過旋轉刻度盤 讓我們進入未來…
By turning the dial to project us ahead in time...
我們能和巴克及朋友們 生活在未來奇妙的世界中
... we're able to be with Buck and friends in the wonderful world of the future.
在那個世界中許多科學 和技術之夢已經成為現實
A world that sees a lot of our scientific and mechanical dreams come true.
你知道吧，巴克沒有任何 超自然或神秘的東西
You know, there's nothing supernatural or mystic about Buck.
他只是個普通的正常人 有著自己的智慧
He's just an ordinary, normal human being who keeps his wits about him.
片名：《未來世界》
主演：唐.彼得.科雷
主演：麥吉.麥克米
主演：伊恩.烏爾夫
導演：喬治.盧卡斯
怎麼啦？ 沒什麼，真的沒問題
- What's wrong? - Nothing, nothing really.
我只是覺得我需要 更強壯的東西
I just feel that I need something stronger.
如果有問題，可以毫不猶豫地請求幫助
If you have a problem, don't hesitate to ask for assistance.
好的，謝謝你，我沒事 呼348-FUN…
- Yes, thank you, I'll be all right. - Call 348-FUN...
怎麼啦？
What's wrong?
別擔心
Never mind.
別擔心.別擔心
Never mind. Never mind.
你能感覺得到嗎？
Can you feel this?
那是什麼呢？噁心嗎？
What is that? Nausea?
現在噁心？
Are you now?
還是曾經有這種感覺呢？
Or have you ever been?
慢點兒動
Move slowly.
喂，那兒有人嗎？
Hello, is somebody else there?
THX，我是內部控制
THX, this is inner control.
你離開了.017到右邊 請糾正
You're off.017 to the right. Correct it, please.
請修正，THX
Make the correction, THX.
好的，向後退，THX1138. 請退後一會兒
All right, then. Just back off, THX 1138. Back off for a second.
好的，請挺住，1138 挺住，挺住，挺住…
- Okay, hold it, 1138. - Hold. Hold. Hold...
怎麼啦？ 我需要更強勁些的
- What's wrong? - I need something stronger.
請服四片紅膠囊.在10分鐘之內 再服兩片，馬上就會幫助你
Take four red capsules. In 10 minutes, take two more. Help is on the way.
怎麼啦？ 我想讓你為此作直觀記錄
- What's wrong? - I want you to take a visual record of this.
我們在補丁細胞中發現了它 我會殺掉它
We found it in the patching cells. We killed it.
你如此盡責，真是謝謝你了
Thank you for being conscientious.
由生物流局…
A visual record is being taken...
將做直觀記錄，並進行存檔 你得…
... and filed with the Department of Biological Flow. You have...
你得退出菲羅茲拉區…
- now out of service in one section of the Filoz era...
由於法律和 規章…
- shall, in any consequence of any law or regulation...
沒有在該工作發揮作用…
... be discharged from such service...
應該向當事人聲稱 這種工作已經到期了
... but shall be delivered up on claim of the party to whom such service may be due.
更高的效率耗能將被標準化
- And greater efficiency, consumption is being standardized.
對不起
We are sorry.
好了，退後吧，THX1138 請後退一會兒
All right then, just back off, THX 1138. Back off for a second.
好了，做出適當的修正
All right, make the appropriate correction.
就是那樣
That's it.
檢查網格線 應該是1239，1239
Check the grid line. Should be 1239, 1239.
好了，看著它 你又會踩到它.會絆倒它
All right, watch it. You're gonna override again. Bring it down.
你就在其旁邊了
You're right next to it.
就是那樣 怎麼啦？
- That's right. - What's wrong?
我昨天剛剛帶了一個來 這不適合我的顧客
I just bought one of these yesterday and it doesn't fit my consumer...
商店裡沒有 其他種類
... and the store doesn't have the other kind.
為了更多的樂趣 及更高的效率…
For more enjoyment and greater efficiency...
損耗必須規範化
... consumption is being standardized.
對不起 這是…
- We are sorry. - This is...
所有崗位，請注意 我遇到暫時性的障礙
Attention all stations, I have a temporary blockage...
這會影響到紅區模塊
... affecting a Red Section module.
在重疊區域 馬上要求完全嵌入
Must demand complete insertion in the override.
這已經到了一個關鍵時刻
It's getting into a critical phase.
出什麼問題了？ 程序及運行環境
- What's wrong? - Comperson and penderal...
3A組非常協調 怎麼啦？爸爸
...are compatible within group 3A. - What's wrong, Papa?
如果你覺得 鎮靜劑的服用不當
If you feel you are not properly sedated...
請馬上呼348-844
... call 348-844 immediately.
如果不成功，可能導致…
Failure to do so may result...
毒品入侵 所帶來的危害
... in prosecution for criminal drug evasion.
偏移…
- A. Excursions...
為了更多的樂趣 及更高的效率
For more enjoyment and greater efficiency...
損耗已經規範化了 對不起
... consumption is being standardized. We are sorry...
這是市探測掃瞄儀
This is city probe scanner.
我們偶遇 某些非常的性活動
We've run across some illegal sexual activity.
現在應該出現在你的DT0屏幕上
It should be on your D TO screen now.
在紅區L14 發生了事故
There has been an accident in Red Sector L 14.
不要放棄自己的崗位 沒有放射洩露的危險
Do not abandon your post. There is no danger of radiation leakage.
重複，紅區L14 發生了意外
Repeat, there has been an accident in Red Sector L 14.
不要放棄自己的崗位 沒有放射洩露的危險
Do not abandon your post. There is no danger of radiation leakage.
6241，那兒的一切進展順利嗎？
6241, is everything all right down there?
紅區L的意外使們損失了63名職員
That accident over in Red Sector L destroyed another 63 personnel...
這使他們損失的人數達242 我方為195人
... giving them a total of 242 lost to our 195.
好好工作 防止意外的發生
Keep up the good work and prevent accidents.
這次輪班已經結束了
This shift is concluded.
性慾較平器誤置在脈衝緩衝器蓋附近
A libido leveler has been mislaid near the pulse-buffering gate.
如果你們意外地.
If you have accidentally...
只有在今天藍色的 樹突細胞只有47個單位
Today only, blue dendrites are only 47 credits. Buy now.
目視雙星可以預知 並改進閱讀能力
Visual binaries now can previse and improve your reading.
你的顧客 有98的因數
Your consumer has a factor of 98.
冷靜
Stay calm.
該電梯暫時不能服務
This elevator has been removed from service.
請乘 您右手邊的電梯
Please use the next elevator on your right.
該電梯暫時不能服務
This elevator has been removed from service.
你用一趟電梯…
Please use the next elevator...
我的時間就是您的
My time is yours.
大眾為了大眾 來吧
- Masses for the masses. - Go ahead.
一個為所有，九九歸一 我們就是大眾
One for all. All is one. Masses are what we are.
我們就是大眾 總而言之，我們就是大眾
We are the masses. But all in all, we are masses.
對於黨及大眾來說，我們就是大眾
For the Party and for all, masses are what we are.
非常好，繼續
Very good. Proceed.
對了…
Well...
我躲過了…
...I slipped...
今天早上的熱能轉換
...on a thermal transfer this morning.
這以前從未有過
It's never happened before.
我沒有好好集中精力
I wasn't concentrating enough.
對，我明白
Yes, I understand.
事情的進展…
Things haven't been...
很不順暢 是，對
...going well. - Yes, fine.
我怎麼出那麼多錯呢？
How could I be so wrong?
我的夥伴…
My mate...
表現非常古怪
...has been acting very strange.
我也說不明白
I can't explain it.
對 我自己也覺得不太自在
- Yes. - I haven't been feeling very well myself.
對，我明白 我也不知道，也許是我吧
- Yes, I understand. - I don't know, maybe it's me.
好，行
Yes, fine.
昨晚我需要一些鎮定劑
I needed some pinural last night.
我覺得似乎.. 太棒了
- I feel as if something... - Excellent.
某些古怪的事兒發生在我的身上
...odd were happening to me.
某些… 是嗎？
- Something that... - Yes?
我不明白的事兒 你能更…
...I can't understand. - Could you be more...
具體一點嗎？
... specific?
鎮靜劑
The sedatives.
我服了藥 但它似乎藥力不夠
I'm taking etracene, but it doesn't seem strong enough.
我很難集中注意力
I have a hard time concentrating.
你是個真實的信徒 保佑這個國家
You are a true believer. Blessings of the state.
請原諒我 保佑大眾
- Please, forgive me. - Blessings of the masses.
你是神的子民 由大眾，因為大眾
Thou art a subject of the divine, created in the image of man...
而被創造成人形
... by the masses, for the masses.
讓我們慶幸一番吧 我們有事可做了
Let us be thankful we have an occupation to fill.
努力工作
Work hard.
增加產出
Increase production.
防止事故
Prevent accidents.
還有…
And...
快樂
... be happy.
如果這能使你快樂， 那也只有這一次
If it will make you happy, just this once.
小心點，很重
Now, be careful, it's heavy.
THX？
THX?
是你嗎？
Is that you?
對不起，但我們得拒絕您的請求
We are sorry, but we must deny your request.
超出五個單元的 出生是不能被允許的
Birthborns are not allowed more than 5 units of enerval.
伊洛瓦代換法的進入…
Substitution of enerval for etracene...
會引起嚴重的 化學失衡
... may cause a serious chemical imbalance.
謝謝你
Thank you.
以前從來沒有 如此滿足過，從來沒有
Never before have we been so contented. Never.
像這樣的龍聲…
A dragon sounds like this when...
九個單元的失諧 沒有…
- nine units of detuned escalatories have not, however...
阻止病毒和軍火 入侵我們的世界
... prevented virus and ordnance from invading our centers.
最近剛剛從9位囚犯中 選定的三位代表已經辭職了
The three recently elected representatives from Con 9 have again resigned...
並回到了自己的部門 你得吃東西
...and returned to their sectors. - You ought to eat.
逃離DD2復原中心的 五個罪犯已經被捕了
Five felons were caught fleeing rehabilitation center DD2.
這五個人 正在接受藥物治療
All five have been undergoing treatment for drug offenses.
這車是你從哪兒弄來的呢？ 我剛剛得到
- Where did you get this car? - I was just issued it.
我已經試車了，並開著它直接 穿過復原中心的人群
I took it for a test drive and ran straight through a crowd at the dispersal center.
噢，真可怕.真可怕
Oh, terrible. Terrible.
不，不，這非常棒
No. No, it was wonderful.
因為我沒有撞到任何人 只撞到了1114
Because I didn't hit anyone, just an 1114.
這是什麼？你為什麼要換掉它呢？
What's this? Why did you change it?
你已經看得夠多了 對了，真是太棒了
- You've seen enough. - Well, that's wonderful.
不，這非常恐怖 你也知道我覺得不太舒服
- No, it's terrible. - You know I don't feel well.
服點鎮靜劑吧 真是太恐怖了，太恐怖了
- Take your sedation. - That is terrible, just terrible.
不，這非常棒，非常出色
No, it was wonderful, wonderful.
因為總之我的手已經癱瘓了
Because my hand, it was paralyzed anyway.
真是有意思
That was very funny.
請記住，服藥過量會導致 嚴重的化學失衡
Remember, an enerval overdose may cause a serious chemical imbalance.
我的時間就是你的
My time is yours.
繼續
Go ahead.
我是怎麼啦？
What's wrong with me?
對於而言，我意味著什麼呢？ 什麼都不是
What am I to her or she to me? Nothing.
是，對 她是個普通的室友
- Yes, fine. - She's an ordinary roommate.
他跟她分享房間
I share rooms with her.
我們的關係是正常的，相融的 對極了
- Our relationship is normal, conforming. - Excellent.
除了空間…
We share nothing...
我們什麼東西都不共享
...but space.
她對我做了什麼？
What is she doing to me?
對，我明白
Yes, I understand.
我覺得自己要死了
I think I'm dying.
你能更…
Could you be more...
具體點嗎？
... specific?
你是個真正的信徒
You are a true believer.
國家的福音
Blessings of the state.
大眾的福音
Blessings of the masses.
你是神的子民 為了大眾…
Thou art a subject of the divine, created in the image of man...
由大眾創造成人形
... by the masses, for the masses.
我們有商業值得我們慶幸
Let us be thankful we have commerce.
買更多，買更多
Buy more. Buy more now.
買…
Buy...
快樂
... and be happy.
怎麼啦？
What's wrong?
怎麼啦？ 別擔心
- What's wrong? - Never mind.
我非常害怕
I was so afraid.
非常孤單
So alone.
多少次…
I wanted to touch you...
我想撫摸你
...so many times.
我幸福
I was happy.
為何要把我捲入進去？
Why get me involved?
他們知道
They know.
他們正看著我們
They've been watching us.
我能感覺到
I can feel it.
沒有人知道
No one knows.
他們現在正看著我們
They're watching us now.
沒有人看到我們
No one can see us.
我能…
I can...
感覺到
... feel it.
二十四
Twenty-four.
二十三
Twenty-three.
二十二
Twenty-two.
6442，請開五號門
6442, gate five, please.
在7A走廊 有位警官出了故障
We've got a malfunctioning officer in corridor 7 A.
好了，就一會兒 準備，1號領域
All right, just a minute. Standby, scope 1.
如果你服用鎮靜劑，你不會 再對我有兩樣的感覺
If you go back on sedation, you won't feel the same way about me.
藥暴力時，你會舉報我
You'll report me for drug violation.
在我的一次輪班時 我會躲過去
I've got a slip movement to install on my next shift.
我不會像現在這樣生活
I'll never make it the way I am now.
我不會出賣你，現在不會
I wouldn't turn you in, not now.
你不會… 我知道自己不會
- You don't... - I know I wouldn't.
沒有入口，你將無法成功
You can do it without etracene.
你能，我知道你能 什麼？
- You can. I know you can. - Then what?
不可能永遠繼續下去，你知道它不能
It can't go on forever, you know it can't.
我們可以離開
We could leave.
我們生活在上層建築中
And live in the superstructure.
你只要輪一次班了， 不是嗎？
You only have one more shift left, don't you?
在下個系列開始前 我們可以離開
We could be gone before the next series started.
好了
It's all right.
行了 準備
- It's all right. - Standing by.
這是什麼？
What's this?
我得見見SEN
I have to see SEN.
我剛剛輪完班
I've just been given a shift change.
何時？ 現在
- When? - Now.
現在？ 他讓我去頂替他的崗位
- Now? - He wants me to come to his quarters.
換班應該 有合理的時間安排
A shift change should come through scheduling.
他為何想見你呢？
Why should he want to see you?
我也不知道
I don't know.
不要去 我得去，他是G34
- Don't go. - I have to. He's a G34.
你不必去
You don't have to.
我不相信他 你得寫報告
I don't trust him. You ought to file a report.
不行
No.
不要惹麻煩
Don't make trouble.
這沒什麼
It's nothing.
那你幹嘛要提出來呢？
Then why did you bring it up?
我沒有
I didn't.
你問我關於卡的事兒
You asked me about the card.
你會給我們 惹麻煩
You're going to get us into trouble.
不要自找麻煩 還有更多細節性的工作
Do not push or shove at the fountain. It's more work for the cleaning detail.
你聽到了嗎？ 機器人，寫的那些東西
- Did you copy that? - The android, the hung-over writing.
他成功了嗎？ 他複製了我嗎？
Is he getting that? Is he copying me?
這是副校長 控制，你有沒有搞到那個密碼呢？
This is borough-flow submaster. Control, have you got that code yet?
接收你的信息非常困難 我查了消息…
I read you very badly. I'll check the message...
23個獵手 是你
- Twenty-three hunter portapods. - It's you.
23個獵手 進來，進來，請坐吧
- Twenty-three hunter portapods. - Come in, come in. Sit down.
真的很古怪 我正在想你哩
You know, this is really odd. I was just thinking about you.
我得為所有的麻煩而道歉 今天早晨，他們搬進來了
I must apologize for all this chaos. They moved in this morning...
一整天都是如此
...and it's been going on all day.
室友被摧毀了，你知道吧
The roommate was destroyed, you know.
極其不便
Terrible inconvenience.
看事物時得高瞻遠矚 做力所能及的事兒
Have to try to see things in perspective, do what you can...
使事物…
...to make things...
恰如其分
...fit.
在每一點上，我能接受事物
I can accept things up to a point.
但是如果你有機會…
But if you get a chance...
做出…
...to make...
調整…
...adjustments...
那拒絕它們，你真是太愚蠢了
...you're very foolish to pass them up.
LUH在哪兒呢？
Where is LUH?
什麼？ 你的卡
- What? - Your card, please.
謝謝你
Thank you.
該監視器是為了特殊目的 或緊急情況而準備的
This monitor is to be used for emergencies or special requests only.
通過安裝好的 電子板…
All routine information can easily be obtained...
可以容易地得到 相關的信息
... through the bulletin panels installed at...
你為什麼讓 LUH來這兒呢？
Why did you have LUH come here?
你怎麼如此關心呢？
Why are you so concerned?
怎麼啦？
What's going on?
我想讓你當我的室友
I want you for my roommate.
我們會善待彼此
We'll be very good for one another.
我不明白，生活…
I don't understand. Living...
生活的選擇已經由計算機設定好了
Living selection is computed.
我知道你在想什麼
I know what you're thinking.
程序的輪換 不也是一種犯罪嗎，對嗎？
Program-shifting isn't that major a crime, is it?
你違規了
You're in violation.
別那樣說
Don't say that.
你對LUH做了什麼？她在這
What have you done to LUH? She was here.
我們…
We...
進行了一次長談
...had a long talk.
她同意你們兩人都調任會更好
And she agreed that it would be better for both of you to switch.
她好像覺得你不是她在 第一地方的最合適配偶
She seemed to think that you weren't accurately mated with her in the first place.
我從未再有過像0NA這樣的助手
I'll never have another mate like ONA.
你對衛生要求非常高，我查過了
You rate very high in sanitation. I've checked.
我不舒服
I don't feel well.
我們會快樂的
We'll be happy.
跟經濟優勢結合的交配結構…
Combined with the economic advantages of the mating structure...
遠遠勝過強化顛倒方面的不利
... it far surpasses any disadvantages in increased perversions.
最後的轉變…
A final trans...
一種寬容和慈善的無窮轉變數學…
An infinite translated mathematics of tolerance and charity...
在人工記憶裝置中就是絕對的二元的
... among artificial memory devices is ultimately binary.
刺激性的花言巧語
Stimulating rhetoric.
LUH？
LUH?
絕對是
Absolute.
手術室的噪音就是我們潛在的證據
The theater of noise is proof of our potential.
原型的流通
The circulation of prototypes.
金色法寶下面是現象
The golden talisman underfoot is phenomenon approaching.
歷史上…
And in the history of now...
所有氣質都是設計好的
... all ethos are designed.
你怎麼在這？你不能來這的
Why are you here? You're not cleared for this area.
我有辦法對付計算機 差不多是想到哪就到哪
You know I have a way with computers. I can program myself for any area, almost.
我會舉報你的
I'll report you.
沒必要為我悲傷
Listen, no need to be distressed with me.
-走吧，不要管我 我已經照顧了LUH
- Get out of here, leave me alone. - I've taken care of LUH.
我把她編到了5450地區
I programmed her to area 5450.
這次調動到下個系列應該會下來
The transfer should come through by the next series.
你需要個新室友
You're gonna need a new roommate.
成績的完美是完美的成績
Performance perfect is perfect performance.
你的輻射率是5…
Your radiation rate is five...
1138，回去
1138, retract.
有東西在接觸TT0綜合邏輯模塊
Something is touching the TTO integrated logic modules.
轉換工具
Switch tools.
1138，怎麼啦？ 你想要效果更強的藥丸嗎？
1138, what's wrong? Would you like a stronger pill?
1138，你在進行高級接觸
1138, you're getting talmod contact.
退回220
Retract at 220.
向量079
Vector 079.
我們在點003處…
We're making contact...
進行接觸
... at.003.
不要越過這個，這是極限
Now, don't override here. This is critical.
好了，你可以下降，就這樣
Okay, you can start your descent. That's it.
慢點，你要超過點7了
Slow down just a little bit. You're overriding.7.
好了，等等，1138
Okay, hold it, 1138.
THX，聽到沒有？THX？
THX, do you read me? THX?
輻射率…
The radiation rate...
為9
...is nine.
THX，你在進入一種危險狀態
THX, you're entering a critical phase.
好的，接觸，就這樣
All right, contact. That's it.
呼吸數據：347，或者加7
Respiratory count: 347, or plus 7.
腎上腺降到點74
Adrenal off.74.
我們收到來自94107操作間 一位高能量操作者
We are receiving an extreme respiratory count from a magnum manipulator...
強烈的呼吸數據
...in operating cell 94107.
-視覺行為不穩定 傳遞控制信息
- Erratic visual behavior. - Transfer control information.
1138當前的腦電波確認為 腎上腺低於點74
Current brain wave confirmation on 1138: Adrenal off.74.
分析：很嚴重
Analyze: Severe.
阻塞說明，請允許我做出修正
An explanation for blocking, so allow me to make correction.
THX，你正進入紅色狀態
You are entering a red phase, THX.
1138遭到嚴重的鎮靜損耗 需要封鎖思維和逮捕
1138 suffering severe sedation depletion, which requires mindlock and arrest.
1138之前剛剛在5241區 交上一個強姦報告
1138 filed a violation report on SEN 5241 immediately prior to...
要求關閉94107號操作間
Request mindlock for operating cell 94107.
編號：1138 姓名：THX
Subject: 1138. Prefix: THX.
關閉受到限制，不要關閉94107
Mindlock restricted. Do not mindlock cell 9410...
提前換崗，重複一次，提前
Priority shift. Repeat, priority...
關閉為繼續
Mindlock pending.
-提前換崗 停止關閉，等等
- Priority shift. - Cut the mindlock. Hold all...
94107號操作間緊急事件
Emergency in cell 94107.
全部疏散，保護所有原子質量
Evacuate all. Secure all atomic mass.
白色級別，重複…
Situation white. Repeat...
白色級別，請把停止關閉好嗎？
... situation white. Will somebody cut the mindlock?
險情取消，險情取消
Clear. Clear.
誰允許先關閉94107大操作間的？
Who permitted a mindlock priority in magnum cell 94107?
取消關閉
Release mindlock.
重新啟動指令監控台，取消關閉
Relapse to command monitor. Release mindlock.
6241，下面沒事吧？沒事吧？
6241, is everything all right down there? Everything all right?
控制中心626對關閉的過失…
Control center 626 holds no responsibility...
不負責任
...for error in mindlock.
控制中心接收器，我是柵極控制中心
Control center's transreceiver, this is grid control.
運行合併H020火焰的動力 阻塞了通訊在
The power run incorporating an H020 flame which blocked communication in the...
你應該在第一時間就報告上來
You should've reported that the minute you first detected it.
所有關閉指令都已傳達給個人，請解除
In any mindlock situation that is already put to character, try and relieve it.
一切都會恢復正常
Everything will be all right.
你由我控制
You are in my hands.
我是來保護你的
I am here to protect you.
你無處可逃
You have nowhere to go.
1138THX被指控強姦…
1138 THX is charged with violation...
附錄445條到613條，索引78.7
... appendix 445 to 613, index 78.7.
吸毒，惡意強姦和犯罪
Drug evasion, malicious sexual perversion and transgression.
根據EC0-TRX314條應該立即處死
Immediate destruction on the basis of an ECO-TRX 314...
這是喪失道德的不能治癒的化學失衡
...incurable chemical imbalance with socially deteriorating conscience.
反對，反對
Reject. Reject.
效率低下的無保證的毀滅
Inefficient, unwarranted destruction.
-必須得到挽救… 他允許色慾存在
- Must be saved... - He's allowed erotics to exist...
-愚蠢，這是起訴的理由嗎？ 但毫無疑問的是
- Inane. What is the prosecution doing? - But there can be no doubt...
-報告顯示他是臨床出身 不適合改造
- Records show he is of clinic origin. - Remotely subject to alteration.
如果社會放過這些不正常人…
If society is to free itself of these deviants...
-這不是種族問題 他必須被毀滅
- This is not a race issue. - He must be destroyed.
我們不必繼續毀滅這些好色之徒
We must not continue to consume these erotics.
我們必須消除罪惡的源泉
We must exterminate the source of sin.
經濟學不必規定這些明顯的宗教情況
Economics must not dictate situations which are obviously religious.
多數獲勝，被告不必被毀滅
Masses won. Defendant used, not destroyed.
休庭
Case rest.
1138，姓名THX…
1138, prefix THX...
顯然無法治癒…
...is pronounced incurable...
應該是有條件的…
... and shall be conditioned...
關在禁閉室裡
... and held in detention.
你是第一次？
Are you now?
還是以前來過？
Or have you ever been?
1642，試試612
1642, try 612.
他好像有個818
He seems to have an 818.
能感覺到這個嗎？
Can you feel this?
4814…
4814...
避開714和2336
...avoid the 714 and the 2336.
好的
All right.
3334，就這樣
3334, that's right.
集中在三-14區
Concentrate on the tri-14 area.
慢點移動
Move slowly.
63410，等待32
63410. Wait for 32.
9.
3437.
Now the 5552.
The 4105.
521上面，122
Above the 521. The 122.
跳過1114
Skip the 1114.
-你覺得怎麼樣，56？
- What do you say, 56? - The 321.
還有21
And 21.
69下面
Under the 69.
夠了
That's enough.
能借你一個通行證嗎？
Can I borrow one of your etracenes?
當然
Sure.
-我覺得這堂課會進行的更好 把這個寫下來，你說45
- I think that the lesson'll go a lot better... - Let's write this up. You said 45 on the...
好吧，我們要把這個放大些嗎？
All right. Should we zoom this a little here?
這個，我剛剛放大了
Here, I'll just zoom it.
不要放大成這樣…？
Hey, doesn't it zoom like...?
你檢查了387級別以上怎麼樣嗎？
Now, what have you been checked out on over at level 387?
在387，我們的系統無法完成，我們通常
Well, at 387, our system was never completed. We'd use...
你沒有過標號8板的經歷嗎？ 沒有
So you haven't any experience with the Mark 8 board? Never...
沒有，不過有過標號7的，你也一樣
No, but with the Mark 7, you had the same...
就只要把它們打開就像 把四個都打開
You could just open them up as if... Open all four up.
是的，你要小心…
Yeah. You ought to be careful about the...
移動傳播方面有什麼極性嗎？你看
You got any polarity here on the mobile travel? Look.
-什麼…？ 我只打開了一個，我打開
- What...? - I just punched up one and I'm opening...
看來378剛剛得到的結果有關係
- imagine that that has something to do with the results the 378 was getting.
就是這個，沒錯，注意看數據，當數據
That's it. Okay, now watch that reading. And as it...
-注意5上面的指針，注意… 這個……這個線團在鬆開
- Watch the needle on 5, now. Watch... - This... This knob is loose.
等等，哪個開關把它弄出來？
Wait, which switch gets it out?
-底部那個 好了，來了
- Master at the bottom. - Okay, there we are.
皮層結合處問題上的真正濃液是什麼？
What is the real dope on the cortex bond problem, anyway?
噢，你發現自己…
Oh, you find yourself with...
-不要讓數據升到4.8以上 看這個
- Don't let it get above 4.8. - Look at this.
-小猴子 我傷到自己
- Little monkey. - I cut myself.
要是你給個雙屏，我加上兩個怎麼辦？
What if you put a dual display on it and I punch two up?
你馬上就能看到兩個 當你看到三個 沖一個三級，看看數字
Yes, you can see two at once. When you see three... Punch a third, you'll see the numbers.
沒錯，最好恢復到兩個 有一個準備讀書
Yeah. So it's best to go back to two. And really, to get an accurate reading...
-我沒看到任何分解 你沒有…
- I don't see any dissolution here. - Well, you haven't...
不要讓它升到4.7
Don't let it get above 4.7.
我會把這些降下來一點
Here, I'll bring these back down a little bit.
-好像超載了 你應該…而不是…
- Yeah, I seem to be overloading it. - Well, you should put... Instead of...
-就這樣，大概4.6，這樣可以吧？ 可以，不過分解是在4.5
- There it is, about 4.6 now. Is that all right? - Yes, but dissolution occurred at 4.5.
噢，是嗎？
Oh, yeah?
你沒事吧？
Are you all right?
他們對你做了什麼
What did they do to you?
什麼？什麼？
What? What?
我懷孕了
I'm going to have a child.
抱住我
Hold me.
-好了，站起來 我們是來幫你的
- Come on, stand up. - We are only here to help you.
-你不必…… 小心
- You have nothing... - Watch it.
好了，我們不想傷害你
Come on, now. We don't wanna hurt you.
放手
Let go.
我們不會傷害你
We won't harm you.
我們只想幫助你
We only want to help you.
3927，你能幫忙抓住他嗎？
3927, could you get him from where you are?
THX1138
THX 1138.
嗨
Hi.
我知道是你把我弄進來的
I know you turned me in.
我在這過得很好
I'm doing quite well here anyway.
我在準備一些事情…
I'm setting some things up...
不過不簡單
...but it isn't easy.
一種非常難的平衡，明白嗎？
A very difficult balance, you know?
我們直接進入主題吧
Listen. Now, let's get something straight right from the start.
瞭解我的整個計劃會需要點時間
It's gonna take you some time to see my overall plan.
所以沒到那時候，不要管你 不明白的東西，明白嗎？
So until then, stay out of things you don't understand, right?
因為你會越幫越忙
You're gonna be making things more difficult for me.
這就是你僅有的作用
It's the least you can do.
你怎麼啦？
What's wrong with you?
-不要這樣 沒事的
- Don't be like that. - It's all right.
你現在安全了
You're safe now.
當後人評判我們的現在的行為
When posterity judges our actions here...
也許不好把我們看作被強迫的戰俘
...it will perhaps see us not as unwilling prisoners...
但是作為人類，不管什麼原因
...but as men who, for whatever reason...
在社會邊緣首先要保留 非貢獻性的個體
...preferred to remain as non-contributing individuals on the edge of society.
-我們不能讓這種事發生無數的轉換
- We must not let this happen. - Countless diversions.
-各位，機會來了 看看我們現在的地方
- Gentlemen, the choice is there. - Reciting where we are.
-爭論離開的問題 不要搞錯了
- Arguing about leaving. - Make no mistake.
-預言未來，荒謬 我們必須選擇一位領袖
- Predicting the future. Ridiculous. - We must choose a leader...
-保持這些東西的可居住性怎麼樣？ 把我們團結起來
- What about keeping things livable here? ...to unite us.
LUH9998 LUH？
- LUH 9998. - LUH?
怎麼啦？誰死了？
What happened? Who's gone?
J0T. 朋友，你的觀點…
- JOT. - My friend, your point of view...
沒錯，中央存儲器，就是這個
Yes, CAM, that's it.
你的觀點很受歡迎，中央存儲器
Your point is well taken, CAM...
不過它缺乏平衡性，經驗 更豐富的就能領導它
...but it lacks the balance that a broader and deeper range of experience can lend it.
我剛來到這時，對一切的 看法跟你差不多
When I first arrived here, I saw things as perhaps you do now.
我對自己的困境感到困惑
Yes, I was confused about my predicament.
我渴望解決，渴望狂奔，渴望毀滅
I longed to thrash out, to tear down, to destroy and annihilate...
渴望破壞，復仇，搶劫
...to ravage, wreak havoc and plunder.
然後作為主要的領導人…
Being basically levelheaded, however...
我意識到自己的第一個目標 應該是熟悉這個地方
...I realized that my first goal should be to study this place...
好像是盲目的環境把我放到了這
...where what seemed blind circumstance had placed me.
聽聽老人的喃喃細語…
Listen to the mumblings of an old man...
通過認真的調查和誠實的 觀察儲存這些激情
...and bank those flames with earnest inquiry and honest observation.
"喃喃細語"
"Mumblings."
"喃喃細語"，你聽到了嗎？ 知道這個演說我們聽了多少次嗎？
"Mumblings," you hear? Know how many times we've listened to that speech?
你知道這個演說我們聽了多少次嗎？
Do you know how many times we've had to listen to that speech?
以為我們跟他一樣盲目 知道你是什麼嗎？
Thinks we're as blind as him. Know what you are?
你讓我噁心，如果我們的 想法跟你一樣
You make me sick. If we thought like you...
你明白我的意思嗎？ 我需要想法，我需要一個想法
You know what I want? I want ideas. I want one idea.
一個可以帶我們離開這的想法！
One idea could get us out of here!
我們只要確定這是正確的想法
We'll just have to be sure it's the right idea.
會找到的，見到它我們就會明白 我看到它就能認出來！
We'll find it. We'll know it when we see it. I'll know it when I see it!
勇往直前，就像你的鼻子一樣
Clear and straightforward and plain as the nose on your face.
跟自己談過後…
Talked to oneself over...
相信他會找到自己快樂的地方
- believed he was going to a place where he'd be happy.
堅定這個信仰，他在這為自己 創造了真正的天堂
And in so believing, he created a veritable paradise for himself right here.
不幸的是，我們不是都能 擁有L00堅定信仰
Unfortunately, not all of us can have the positive conviction of LOO.
不過非常感謝的是，不是所有人 被SEN的兇兆壓制了
But, thankfully, not all of us are burdened with the ominous forebodings of SEN.
我自己…
I, myself...
這就是我對錯誤想法的意思
Now, that's what I mean by the wrong idea.
我不打算證明歷史的有效性
Look, I'm not going to try to prove the usefulness of history.
很顯然這是不需要證明的
It is genuinely too obvious to need proof.
我想幫助你
I want to help you.
你可以幫助我
You can help me.
拿著
Here.
拿著一塊點心
Take a biscuit.
你知道，我們都在一條船上
You understand, we're all in this together.
你想離開，你不像他們
You want to leave. You're not like them.
我希望看到我們都離開這
I'll see to it that we all get out of here.
別緊張！看看他們 又可憐，又令人同情
Take it easy! Look at them. It's pathetic. It's pitiful.
他們甚至到我的角落裡尋找東西
They've even begun to go into my corner and look for things.
我的東西
My things.
你跟我一條陣線
You're with me.
我知道
I know.
我有份合同
I have a contract.
上面說…
All it says is:
"你跟我在一條陣線"
"You're with me."
我們在一條船上了
We're all in this together.
我們必須說服其他人
We must convince the others.
那待會兒再說
Later, then.
我們需要新的聯合
We need a new unity.
不是聯合阻礙異議
And not a unity which discourages dissent.
我們需要異議，但我們 需要創造性的異議
We need dissent, but we need a creative dissent.
我們的聲音和諧中出現的…
Our voices are not raised in any harmonious chorus...
但我們的區別重點的區別 不是基本的區別
...but our differences are differences of emphasis rather than of fundamentals.
-明天，當我們… 五名6431399
- Tomorrow, as we... - Nondescript 6431399.
-什麼東西？ 一個矮子
- What is it? - A shell dweller.
他們生活在外殼中，非常獨特
They live in the outer shell. Quite unique.
以前這有兩個，他們有氣味
There have been two here before, and they smell.
你知道嗎？
What do you know?
過來，朋友
Come here, my friend.
讓我摸摸你
Let me touch you.
他剛剛做了什麼
What'd he just do?
怎麼啦？
What's wrong, huh?
你的午餐髒了，真浪費
Your lunch is dirty. What a waste.
還有些可以吃
Here, we can save some of it.
沒事
It's all right.
一切都會好的
Everything's fine.
幹嘛？
What?
如果你不想到，幹嘛要接啊？
Well, if you didn't want it, why'd you take it?
我以為每個人都有
I thought this was all settled.
-你去哪？ 我要走
- Where you going? - I'm leaving.
走？走什麼？你不能走
Leaving? Leaving what? You can't leave.
你不能走，嘿，等等
You can't go. Hey, wait.
噢，我明白了，氣味，真難聞
Oh, I know, the smell. Yeah, it's terrible.
有點…
It's a little bit...
嘿，你不能…你不能就這樣走…
Hey, you can't... You can't leave without...
等等
Just a minute.
等等，就等一下
Wait. Just wait there a minute.
經過深思熟慮，我覺得出去…
After long deliberation, I have decided to go out...
親自檢查柵欄…
...and personally examine the barrier...
瞭解第一手的困難…
...to learn firsthand what difficulties are involved...
並決定如何克服它們 我承認這有危險
...and decide how to overcome them. I recognize an element of risk...
但這樣的時刻需要做出決定，採取行動
...but moments such as these require that a choice be made and action taken...
別顧及危險了.我們不久回來…
...regardless of the danger. We'll be back soon...
但是我們會找到一個可以出去的口子
...but we'll be gone long enough to form an accurate and functional escape.
我會有一個真誠的想法指導這次工作
And I shall have an honest idea how best to organize us into a working unit.
新隊組合.難以置信
- The new alignment. - Incredible.
等等.嘿.等我啊
Wait. Wait. Hey, wait for me.
擺正事情.讓他們知道誰是領導者
Just the thing to put them on their feet. Show them who the leaders are.
當我們回來時，他們會在那裡的 會在我的手掌心的
When we get back, they'll be right there, right in the palm of my hand.
毫無疑問的 就算老PT0跟著我們
There's no question. Even old PTO would be with us...
如果他仍然建議
...if he'd still been advised.
我們走了多遠了.知道嗎？
How far before they can't see us anymore, huh?
也許我們最好坐在這裡
Maybe we better sit down right here.
嘿.休息一下
Hey, rest for a while.
我不能…
I can't...
我看不見任何人
I can't see them anymore.
LUH
LUH.
你在追求LUH，是嗎？
You're going after LUH, aren't you?
哇，太可笑
Why, it's ridiculous.
追求…
Going after...
噢.等等.有些事我不必須得告訴你
Oh, wait, I knew there was something I had to tell you.
LUH，你知道的.另一個 新人LUH嗎？
LUH, you know, the other...? The new LUH?
他告訴我他已經看到她了 他在來這裡前看到她過
He told me he'd seen her. He saw her just before he came out here.
她會來這裡的 她怎樣了？
- She's gonna be coming out here. - How was she?
噢.很好.健康著呢 就是這條路
Oh, very well. Very good health. Just exactly the way...
你在撒謊.不.我沒有
- You're lying. - No, I am not.
空氣變的稀薄
The air's getting thinner.
或者是大氣壓變的很強
Or pressure's getting greater.
是大氣壓
It's the pressure.
你感覺如何？
How do you feel?
Shouldn't be this far.
不應該走遠
沒有空氣
There's no air.
我沒有時間了 如果你喜歡你就呆在這
I haven't got the time. You can stay here if you like.
我願意跟著你
I'll come with you.
那是什麼？
What?
瞧
Look.
瞧什麼？
What?
有個人呢
That's a man.
是個男的，在揮手 他在向我們揮手
It's a man. He's waving. He's waving to us.
嗨
Hi.
你好
Hello.
你們從哪裡來？
Where'd you guys come from?
噢.是的.那沒什麼的 那是吃的嗎？
Oh, well, it doesn't make any difference. Is that food?
我餓了.不介意吧？
I'm starving. Do you mind?
你怎麼到這裡來的？
How did you get here?
我是說.我迷路了
I mean, I was lost.
你現在迷路了嗎？
You're not lost now?
知道出口嗎？
Know the way out?
在那裡.那是我們開始的地方
- That's the way out. - That's the way we came.
是的.也許你們在打圈圈.那是出口
Yeah, but maybe you were traveling in circles. That's the way out.
你如何知道的？
How do you know?
那好.瞧瞧去
Well, look.
走近點.看到了嗎？
Look more closely. You see?
來吧
Come on.
來啊
Oh, yeah.
沒什麼能阻擋我們
Nothing stopped us.
來
Come on.
這是出口
Here's a doorway.
保持通道暢通
Keep causeways clean.
節省時間.保住生命
Save time. Save lives.
保持通道暢通
Keep causeways clean.
節省時間.保住生命
Save time, save lives.
保持通道暢通
Keep causeways clean.
節省時間.保住生命
Save time, save lives.
保持通道暢通
Keep causeways clean.
節省時間.保住生命
Save time, save lives.
保持通道暢通
Keep causeways clean.
節省時間.保住生命
Save time, save lives.
你好.12. 神經指令艙.我是安全部門b
- Hello, 12. - Synapse module, this is security B.
回話，神經指令艙？
Read me, synapse module?
中轉系統必須…
Research into relay system must be given...
做早期可行性報告
- intercerebral process reported earlier.
新的環境下計劃的如何？
How shall the new environment be programmed?
發生的很慢…
It all happened so slowly that...
大多數人根本沒意識到有事發生
...most men failed to realize that anything had happened at all.
我想知道SEN發生什麼事
I wonder what happened to SEN.
我們從不那樣做
We'll never make it through that main way.
你是誰？我是全息圖
- Who are you? - I'm a hologram.
我不是真的.你知道的 白日做夢…
I'm not real. You know, the fantasy bureau...
所有的都得需要電池維持
...electrically-generated realities and all that.
我在電路裡憋的太久
I was stuck in the same circuit for too long.
你看到那個胳膊和腿了嗎？
The arm and leg routine, did you see that one?
我一直是屬於現實世界
I always wanted to be part of the real world.
所以我要走
So I left.
嗨.瞧瞧
Hey, look.
你瞎忙碌
You are engaged in an unauthorized procedure.
記住你在哪裡.這是…
Remain where you are. This...
我們在k8身上發現一個U65
We have a U65 on a K8.
轉移未被授權的聯繫…
Transfer all unauthorized contacts...
在區域688Con-G 到中心之間.模式為7
...in precinct 688 Con-G to this center, mode 7.
鏈接DD，NEC-08.開始
Termination of exurban links DD, NEC-08.
這趟火車將在5分鐘內 返回中央網絡部
This tram will return to the Central Web in five minutes.
我是辦918案子.編號91021 我們需要援助
This is 91021 on case 918. We are going to need assistance.
這是電子受限區域
This is an electronic-restricted area.
會有3名長官來
It would be nice to have three additional officers.
你看到他們了嗎？ 沒有.他們定是在區域9
- Have you seen them? - No. They must be somewhere in group 9.
執行5271
Operation 5271.
預算控制.我們要對THX1138 做成本估算
Budget Control, we'd like a cost analysis on the THX 1138 account.
包括利息和膨脹指數
Include all interest and inflation percentages.
支出為649.還在上升中
Expenditures are 649 and rising.
那是什麼？定是高速公路
- What was that? - Must be an expressway.
預算控制部.在THX上的支出 額度為14，000元
This is Budget Control. The expenditure ceiling on the THX case is 14,000 credits.
記住.不要超出預算
Remember, thrifty thinkers are always under budget.
喜歡這個嗎？不值錢
Would you like part of this? It's not very much.
這些人你都知道嗎？
Did you know all the insides are gone from all these people?
中斷
Halt.
經濟學告之需要中止操作…
Economics make it necessary to terminate any operation...
超出原來預算5%
... which exceeds 5 percent of its primary budget.
支出是1000並在上升中
Expenditures are 1000 and rising.
事情看起來沒有意義
Things don't seem to make sense.
有時.我看出事情的端倪…
Sometimes I see things get left out...
它們不適合
...and they don't fit.
人們瞧不出它們來
People don't seem to see them.
或者他們不知道做什麼
Or they don't know what to do.
有時我…
Sometimes l...
有時一點點…
Sometimes little...
一點點變動…
A little adjustment...
能改變所有的不同
...can make all the difference.
我想做正確的事情
I wanna do the right thing.
我想回去
I wanna go back.
我…我…
I... I...
我能…我要開始
I can... I can start again.
我能改變
I can change.
我能夠…我能得救
I can... I can help.
我只想要一段…
I just need a...
只想休息一段時間
Need to rest up for a little while.
這不是祈禱之所
This is no place for prayer.
如果你要對0MM懺悔 你要戴上金屬圈.你知道的
If you want to speak to OMM, you must go to a unichapel, you know that.
是的.什麼？
- Yeah. - What?
你有麻煩嗎？ 不.我很好.我現在就走
- Are you in any trouble? - No. I'm okay. I'm going now.
你多少號還有你的叫什麼？ 我要報告上去
What's your number and your prefix? I'm gonna see this gets into your report.
不.我現在就走
No, I'm leaving now.
抱歉.我必須得報告所有的入侵者
I'm sorry, I have to report all intruders.
你的鑒定徽章在哪裡？ 我丟了
- Where's your identification badge? - I lost it.
你違法了 我必須報告給你的上司
You're in violation. I'll have to report you to the authorities.
不.那不關我的事 不要.求你了
- No, it's not my time. - Please, just...
收集
Trapped.
看來僅有的出路是剛進來的那條
Looks like the only way out is the way we came in.
你還有什麼吃的嗎？我餓了
Say, do you have any more of that food? I'm hungry.
她不在那裡
She's not there.
你在找誰？
Who are you looking for?
你們能聽到我說話嗎？ 冷靜，事情會得到很好處理的
Can you hear me? Stay calm. Everything will be all right.
門眼看起來被塞住了
The door seems to be jammed.
雷達自動跟蹤
Please check the lock on your side.
事情會得到很好處理的 我們來幫助你們
Everything will be all right. We are here to help you.
鎮定
Stay calm.
我們不會傷害你們
We are not going to harm you.
事情都會得到很好處理的
Everything will be all right.
是的.除非計算機有誤…
Well, unless that computer has made a mistake...
那是你的密友
...that's your roommate.
不.不.你錯了
No. No, you're wrong.
我希望那個金屬板有用
I hope that auxiliary load holds.
我幾乎完電路板
I'm almost through to the upper positive plates.
電路板？
Upper positive plates?
也許你是對的 也許計算機哪裡出了問題
Maybe you are right. Maybe there's something wrong with the computer.
我不知道.好奇怪的事情
I don't know. It's a strange life.
控制論.遺傳說.激光學.等等
Cybernetics, genetics, lasers and all those things.
我猜我永遠都不會理解那碼子事
I guess I'll never understand any of that stuff.
也許全息圖也沒作用
Guess maybe holograms are not supposed to.
THX1138將做最小貨幣支出考慮
THX 1138 will be taken into custody at a minimal monetary expenditure.
總共成本：預算為6000
Total operation cost: 6000 credits under budget.
祝賀.太有效率
Congratulations. Be efficient...
開心的很.謝謝你
...be happy. - Thank you.
你在那裡好嗎？
Are you all right in there?
疏散中心21區域 飛行線路發生改變
Proceed to dispersal center 21. Projected route of flight will be transferred.
鏈接DD，NEC-08.開始
Termination of exurban links DD, NEC-08.
這趟火車將在5分鐘內 返回中央網絡部
This tram will return to the Central Web in five...
那是什麼？電感器？
What is that? An inducer?
它壞了？是的
- Did it fall off? - Yeah.
如何…？瞧.你做什麼？
- How...? - Look out. What're you doing?
噢.抱歉.對不起
Oh, sorry. Excuse me.
你好
Hello.
讓我再瞧瞧 我想我能搞定它
Let me see that again. I think I have it.
來.伸出胳膊
Here, give me your arm.
你知道的…
You know...
我以前上學時是非常艱苦的
...when I was at school, it was all very different.
我們那時常常躺在床上 為經濟考慮…
We used to stay in bed all the time. Combined primary economics...
插上這個大大的瓶子
Combined primary economics was a bottle about this big.
一個星期
Took a week.
和5241SEN可視聯繫
A visual contact with 5241 SEN.
兩名警官會逮捕討厭的SEN
Two officers to pick up felon SEN.
警官1088，在恢復護中…
Officer 1088, proceed with recovery...
討厭的5241SEN.當前位置
...of felon 5241 SEN. Current position...
我們對它的分貝做了分析
- sure to report all decibel surges in excess of one point...
在你的區域帶.他不會呆3分鐘
... in your zoned section for longer than three minutes.
噴氣式加速在疏散區域對個人不安全
Jet acceleration will not be safe to persons in dispersal area.
為避免加速.請不要在右邊坐車
To avoid being singed by jet exhaust, please exit your vehicle on the right...
去左邊藍色地帶走路
... and walk through the blue zone on the left.
沒有配備燃燒室…
- Is not equipped with afterburner...
不要在疏散區泊車
... you are not to park in the inner dispersal area.
這個區受限
- Temporarily restricted in this area.
超速車型364 方位簡稱A1Z，具體是14B1C
Centerex ancillary number 364. Southbound A 1 Z, that was 14B 1 C.
超速車型預備行駛
Critical noise levels in this area.
但要確定分貝指數…
Be sure to report all decibel surges...
氣缸1.5 啟動…
... in excess of 1.5 on the Murrer-Wiggins scale.
如果你想開.請按左鍵
- And stand to the right. If you wish to pass, please do so on the left.
實時監控…
Cabaret and Fourstar vehicles at the observation...
出現交通事故…
There's been an accident in level...
我要走高速公路
I think I ran over a Wookiee back there on the expressway.
指令中心
Central, Central Control.
統計系統傳輸數據顯示出K34…
- New statistical method used to test the construction of the K34 determiner...
馬力為J20節
... proves its analogy to the J20 series.
在821區域有交通事故
We have an accident in 821.
罪犯車靠3T成分助推
Felon vehicle is a 3T Support.
罪犯沒在車中
Felon is not in vehicle.
可改變
Changeable.
可變的
Alterable.
性情不定的
Mutable.
有變數的
Variable.
萬能的
Versatile.
可模壓的
Moldable.
活動的
Movable.
波動的
Fluctuate.
起伏的
Undulate.
閃動的
Flicker.
擺動的
Flutter.
跳動的
Pulsate.
搖擺的
Vibrate.
交替的
Alternate.
可塑性的
Plastic.
185，26路，185區， 對的
- 185, group 26, corner 185, that is correct.
清理交通事故
Clear traffic in central left web.
還有300距離
Officers are 300 and closing.
還有285距離
Officers are 285 and closing.
支出10000，還在上升中
Expenditures are 10,000 and rising.
支出為…
Expenditures are...
還有270距離
Officers are 270 and closing.
212，在b路段上.有太多車了
- 212, too many vehicles on code B.
1138被顯示在高速公路上停下
1138 appears to have stopped on expressway...
還有205距離
Officers are 205 and closing.
還有195距離
Officers are 195 and closing.
還有185距離
Officers are 185 and closing.
還有170距離
Officers are 170 and closing.
還有165距離
Officers are 165 and closing.
還有160距離
Officers are 160 and closing.
還有155距離
Officers are 155 and closing.
還有150距離
Officers are 150 and closing.
還有140距離
Officers are 140 and closing.
那車時速115.上了高速公路300
Vehicle's at 115, approaching Expressway 300.
好的.那麼.我會 在程序1中觀察他
All right, then, I'm gonna... See him on scope 1.
這是脈衝
- Into the internal-module control pulses, a nine.
這是619
Now, this is the 619.
新商標6071
A brand-new 6071.
這些是緩衝器信號…
This lodging network converts the buffered memory signals...
受限高速公路.那車裝備了 衛星反導彈觀測系統
I have a vehicle entering a restricted-access expressway. Vehicle is a Samos 3.
支出為14，000
Expenditures are 14,000.
有情況.這些指令…
I'll show you. These modules are made by...
你已經超出預算
You have just exceeded your primary budget.
停下車
Stop your vehicle.
你接近工作區域了.停車
You are approaching a work area. Stop your vehicle.
那是條受限高速公路.停車
You are traveling in a restricted-access expressway. Stop your vehicle.
聽到沒有？聽到沒有？
Do you read? Do you read?
他向隧道400建築物駛去
He appears to be headed for that construction site at tunnel 400.
接近障礙物區…
Approaching the restricted area...
速度每小時235公里
... at 235 miles per hour.
車子急速向障礙物區行駛…
I have a vehicle entering a restricted-access express...
人員請散開.危險區.危險區
- Construction personnel, evacuate area. - Evacuate area.
控制台.他在障礙物區
Control, he's in the area.
他現行駛在高速公路…
He's now passed into expressway...
向障礙物區行駛
He appears to be headed for that construction site.
任務控制…
Mission control...
我們追丟了他
We've lost him.
你能在視頻上發現他嗎？謝謝
Can you pick him up on the electroscan? Thank you.
我們配備了聲納系統
We have a sonar fix on subject.
是的.我們聽到了.就是他
- Yes, we hear it. - That's him.
聽上去像個金屬容器
It sounds like shell dwellers.
他逃離這個城市 重複，他要逃離這個城市
He appears to be heading outside the city. Repeat, he is heading outside the city.
我能做的是給你建議
All I can do is note your information.
行動
Stand by.
請回來.不要害怕
Please come back. You have nothing to be afraid of.
THX為6%超出了預算 案子要中止
The THX account is 6 percent over budget. The case is to be terminated.
中止操作
Discontinue operation.
向62位置報告
Report to thermal station 62.
中止操作
Discontinue operation.
我們必須回去
We have to go back.
這是你最後一次和我們回去的機會了
This is your last chance to return with us.
你無處可去
You have nowhere to go.
離開這個城市你無法生存
You cannot survive outside the city shell.
我們僅僅是想幫你
We only want to help you.
這是你最後的機會
This is your last chance.
[ENGLISH]